EDIKURNIAWAN

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a hard worker with experience as a web developer. I love coding so I study every day to improve my skills regarding web development. My experience is related to web development for about 1 year using several technologies to build websites from clients request.

PHONE

+62 813 5040 0660

EMAIL

edikurniawan.dev@gmail.com

PERSONAL WEBSITE

https://edikurniawan.pages.dev

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/edikurniawan-dev

GITHUB

https://github.com/edikurniawan-dev

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Python

PHP

Git

TailwindCSS

Bootstrap

ReactJS NodeJS

Laravel

Liwewire

WordPress

Elementor

MvSQL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics with GPA 3.38 of 4.00, Institut Teknologi Sumatera August 2017 - July 2021

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Web Developer at CV. Newus Teknologi

November 2021 - March 2022

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Laravel, Livewire, cPanel

- Develop web apps from client request
- Deploy web apps to server using shared hosting

Frontend Web Developer at PT. Banopolis Inovasi Kendara

June 2020 - July 2020

Technologies: HTML, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SweetAlert

Develop the Jaramba Admin Dashboard display which functions to monitor the location of the bus that is running. In addition it stores route data, driver, bus and bus trip history

Computer Lab Assistant at Institut Teknologi Sumatera

February 2019 - November 2020

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, Excel, Linux

Teaches basic courses in Web Programming, Introduction to Computers and Software 2 and Operating Systems

PROJECTS

PPDB SMA Perintis 2 Bandar Lampung - Web Application (FullStack Developer)

Technologies: Laravel, Livewire, Bootstrap, MySQL

- Develop a dashboard admin to manage student registration
- Display chart of percentage student registration

Sistem Informasi Tata Ruang Lampung Utara - Web Application (FullStack Developer)

Technologies: Laravel, Livewire, TailwindCSS, MySQL

- Develop the login, register and forget password sections.
- Develop dashboard admin to manage incoming application letter
- Display location on ArcGIS Map

Cash Gampang - Web Application (FullStack Developer)

Technologies: Laravel, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, MySQL

- Develop page of Cash Gampang and dashboard admin to manage content
- Develop website fully responsive

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Secretary at Division Kemitraan dan Kerjasama in Generasi Baru Indonesia (GenBI)

2019 - 2020

Video Editor at Division Kreasi Dakwah Madani in Mahasiswa Peradaban Islam (Madani)

2018 - 2020

Public Relations at Himpunan Pelajar Matematika (HIPATIKA) SMAN 2 Kotabumi

2016 - 2017